and I say that Ukraine is a country of the ASR so
а я говорю то что Украина страна АСР так
look, you think we
смотри это вы считаете мы
are restoring Kievan Rus Yes,
восстанавливаем Киевскую Русь Да
our historical lands Yes, Smolensk,
исторические наши земли Да Смоленск
Bryansk Yes, Ryazan, Moscow, Vladimir, Suzdal,
Брянск Да Рязань Москва Владимир Суздаль
these are all the cities that the Kyiv princes made
это все города которые сделали киевские
Hello Yes, good evening, you talk about the World Cup,
здравствуйте Да Добрый вечер о ЧМ
yes, about different things, for example, about
общаетесь да так о разном на пример о
board games like Warhammer
настольных играх из разряда Warhammer
40,000 Fantasy Battle and Old World yeah ...
40.000 Fantasy Battle и Old World угу ну
topic how do you feel about the
Давайте предлагать тему как относитесь к
fact that Russia attacked
тому что Россия напала на
Ukraine and how it is
Украину м как к
inevitable What is the
неизбежному В чём
inevitability of the failure to implement the Ukrainian and
неизбежность невыполнение украино и
Minsk
минских
uh so Minsk Russia so not Minsk and
ээ так мински Россия так не мински и
Russia violated immediately after signing
Россия нарушила сразу как подписала
look it's all visible we open
посмотрите это ж всё видно открываем
we open those listen look at the Minsk
открываем те по слушай смотри минские
agreements and immediately after signing of the
соглашения и сразу после подписания
Minsk agreements through  Russia violated
минских соглашений через Россия нарушила
the Ceasefire and immediately captured Debaltseve after 3
Перемирие и сразу же захватило через 3
days Look at the dates m we
дня дебальцева Посмотри по датам м
open we open Look now I
открываем открываем Смотри сейчас я тебя
open you Look here we open Especially
открываю Смотри вот открываем Специально
for you
для тебя
so so
так так
Opa so
Опа так
so here are the Minsk agreements that you
так вот минские соглашения те которые вы
second want to say now they were
вторые хотите сейчас сказать они были
signed on February 11-12  2015 Yes, everything
подписаны 11-12 февраля 2015 года Да всё
stopped the fighting and then
остановка боевых действий и тут же
Russia disrupted them by capturing Debaltseve Yes,
Россия сорвала их захватив дебальцева Да
Debaltseve was captured on
дебальцева было захвачено 18 до
February 18, 2015, that is,
18 до 18 февраля 2015 года то есть
look, Ukraine, Ukraine signed the Minsk
смотри Украина Украина подписала минские
agreements and
соглашения и
Stop the fighting between Russia,
Останови боевые действия между Россией
Ukraine, don't try Zabava Well, Rub between
Укра не пытайся Забава Ну Потри между
whom and  who signed the Minsk
кем и кем были подписаны минские
agreements between the BCE and Russia
соглашения так между между бсе и Россией
and Ukraine
а Украина Гарант
was the guarantor that well there are three signatures of the OSCE Russia
была что ну там три подписи обсе Россия
they agreed on a ceasefire that
они договорились о прекращении огня что
Russia withdraws its troops and introduces an
об Россия выводит свои войска а вводит
observer mission and Ukraine was the
наблюдатель миссию а Украина была
guarantor of these
гарантом этих
agreements you are
соглашений ты
now turning on no by Show  I know in the
вот сейчас включаешь нет по Покажи мне в
Minsk agreements that Ukraine  - this is a
минских соглашениях что Украина - это
participant of the Minsk
участник минских
agreements how much do their signatures cost
соглашений сколько чии подписи стоят
open open open show Ukraine
открывай открыва открывай покажи Украина
- this is the Guarantor Open the Minsk
- это Гарант Открой минские
agreements Ukraine Guarantor signed
соглашения Украина Гарант подписана
between the OSCE and Russia Zurabov signed
между обсе и России зурабов подписал
yours in his
ваш в своём
[music]
[музыка]
repertoire Show Ukraine
репертуаре Покажи Украина
Guarantor there they even sent an unofficial
Гарант туда даже отправили неофициальное
observer just some former
наблюдателя просто какого-то бывшего
president  ku he is not even an official Nikoy
президента ку он даже не чиновник Никой
was from Russia was the official
был от России был официальный
representative of Zurabov Yes the ambassador from the OSCE
представитель зурабов Да посол от обсе
was the official representative of Tavi Yes and
был официальный представитель Тави Да а
from Ukraine who in short just came as an observer
от Украины кто короче просто наблюдатель
because we were the guarantors Come on
приехал потому что мы гаранты были Давай
open the Minsk agreements Look who
открывай минские соглашение Смотри кто
signed the participants of the three-party
подписал участники трёх сторонней
contact group Ambassador
контактной группы посол
Heidi Talia  blame the second president
Хайди талья вини второй президент
ui he is not an official person he has
уи он не официальное лицо он уже давно
not been president for a long time so on and the third who is not
не президент так дальше и третий кто нет
At that time it was an official person
На тот момент это было официальное лицо
No he was not an official person of the
Нет он не был официальным лицом
president he was not president
президента он не был уже президентом
for a long time
давным-давно
After him there was already Yushchenko After him there was
После него уже был Ющенко После него был
Yanukovych  and so on And even so, who would
Янукович и так дальше А даж так кем бы
Kuchma have been at the time of signing these
Кем был Кучма в момент подписания этих
agreements, he simply came as an observer
соглашений он просто как наблюдатель
from Russia, who signed, who
приехал от России кто подписал кто от
signed from Russia, come on  don't leak who is from
России подписал давай не сливай кто от
Russia from ro from Russia Zurabov Zurabov
Росси от ро от России зурабов зурабов
who read how it is written his position is the
кто читай как написано его должность
Ambassador of the Russian
посол Российской
Federation in Ukraine everything is in Ukraine
Федерации в Украине всё в Украине даже
not even in Ukraine but in Ukraine the truth is there is
не на Украине а в Украине правда там на
well in now it's look it turns out from
ну на в сейчас это смотри получается от
Russia they sent an ambassador an official person
России прислали посла официальное лицо
from the OSCE  Talvi was sent, not an official
от обсе прислали талви не официальное
person Because Russia and the OSCE signed the
лицо Потому что Россия и обсе заключила
Minsk agreements Yes,
минские соглашения Да от Украины приехал
not a single official came from Ukraine, no one
ни один чиновник от Украины не
participated there, no one signed,
участвовал там не подписывал подписал
some former president of
какой-то бывший президент
Ukraine Kuchma signed, he was nothing, neither a
Украины Кучма он он не был ни чено ни
deputy, nor a minister, nor an ambassador, nor a
депутатом ни министром ни послом ни
president, he  just came as an observer
президентом он просто как наблюдатель
because Ukraine was a guarantor
приехал потому что Украина была гарантом
because it happened on the territory of Ukraine
потому что это на территории Украины
that's all And what's wrong
происходило вот и всё А что не так
show me where Ukraine is named in the Minsk
покажи мне где Украина в минских
agreements as a
соглашениях названо
participant between whom and to what the conflict between the OSCE
участник между кем и к шл конфликт между
between NATO and
обсе между НАТО и
Russia between NATO and Russia since the
Россией между НАТО и Россией с
fourteenth  years conflict
четырнадцатого года конфликт
Hello collective West in the person of Obse tali
Алло коллективный запад в лице обсе тали
vini and Russia also Putin Listen is fighting
вини и Россия то ж Путина Послушай воюет
with the collective
с коллективным
West If there was a conflict with Russia and
западом Если б шёл конфликт с Россией и
Ukraine  yes then Ukraine would have had everything already
с Украиной да тогда бы Украине всё уже
what are you for Come on
бы было кие взят что ты за Давай
arguments Hello Don't leak I'm all disgraceful
аргументы Алло Не сливай я все позорно
mine Don't leak don't leak yes yes
свае Да не сливай не сливай да да сейчас
leak now well really look from you there was an
сливай ну реально смотри от вас был
official ambassador from the OSCE there was an
официальный посол от обсе было
official person from Ukraine
официальное лицо от Украины приехал
just some kind of person came  then the guy who
просто какой-то мужик который когда-то
was once an official because he
был чиновником потому что он как
came as an observer Ukraine was simply a
наблюдатель приехал Украина просто была
guarantor of the
гарантом
German such a question You, let's say
неме такой вопрос Ты допустим
Well, you've already
Ну уже
been exposed to many
засветился много у
people you,
кого ты
let's say, no cut no cut you are now
допустим не среза не не среза ты сейчас
middle Everything you lost you have no no no I do
сре Всё ты проиграл у тебя нет нет нет я
n't have you  I'll let you in Let's give you opened your mouth for
тебя не пущу Давай даём ты открыл рот за
Minsk Let's finish off Minsk You all
Минский Давай мы добьём мински вы все
give it up until the surrender I'm telling you again Look
отдаете так до сда я ещё раз говорю
So you ask between whom and whom
Смотри Значит ты спроси между кем и кем
I'm telling you between Russia and the OSCE
я тебе говорю между Россией и обсе
because the war was between Russia as the
потому что война шла между Россией как
Soviet Union and the collective West
советским союзом и коллективным западом
NATO  Ukraine was the guarantor because
НАТО Украина была гарантом потому что
this battle took place on its
эта битва происходила на её
territory Show me in these Minsk
территории Покажи мне в этих минских
agreements Where was there even one
соглашениях Да где был хоть один
official representative of Ukraine there
представитель официальный Украины не
was not a single official
было ни одного чиновника не
Well, let's go to the first point  I'll
было Ну вот давай первый же пункт
read the point again, look, this is your
прочитаю ещё раз пункт смотри Это ваши с
relationship with the OSCE, you signed up for the OSCE, you and the
обсе отношения вы подписались обсе вы с
OSCE and figure it out, we are the Ukraine
обсе и разбирайтесь в пункты мы Украина
Guarantor, we
Гарант мы обязательства на себя вообще
didn't take on any obligations at all, we just came,
никакие не брали мы просто приехали
sent Kuchma, just a guy who
послали кучму просто мужика который
was once president, because he
когда-то был президентом потому что он
seemed to know these guys  all the men Yes, so that he
вроде знал этих всех мужиков Да чтобы он
could see that they didn't overdo it and
посмотрел чтобы они не пересолили есь и
signed something in Minsk Yes, what's the
что-то подписали в Минске Да в чём
problem Ukraine is not a party to the
проблема Украина не есть стороной
conflict in this Ukraine was not a
конфликта в этом Украина не была
party to the conflict
стороной конфликта
uh, the conflict was between NATO and the
ээ конфликт был меж между НАТО и
Russian Federation between NATO and Russia
Российской федераци между НАТО и Россией
Well, what  how how are you jumping with st
Ну а что как как ты вот прыгаешь со ст
fighting with who are you fighting with now who are you
воюет с кем вы сейчас воюете с кем вы
fighting with who are you fighting with Stop Stop let's
воюете с кем вы воюете Стоп Стоп давай
stop open Minsk open Minsk
стоп открываем мински открываем мински
25 read out the first point in full Why do we need a
25 зачитывать полностью первый пункт
point if we didn't
Зачем пункт если мы его не
sign it why should I read the point do you
подписывали зачем мне читать пункт ты
want you Read it out  Read it to the obse
хочешь ты Зачитай ты Зачитай в обсе
send it like Why should I read it if
посылай типа Вы зачем мне читать н если
you signed it read why why
вы подписывали их читай зачем зачем
explain why read I don't want do you want to
Объясни Зачем читай я не хочу ты хочешь
read No I don't want to read you need to you
читать Нет я не хочу читать тебе надо ты
read  you see you are being cut off you
читать видишь Ты срезается ты сейчас
will be now you need you to
будешь тебе надо ты
read I don't need to read I don't need to
прочитать мне не надо читать мне не надо
read you I suggest reading Why do
читать тебе предлагаю прочитать Зачем
you suggest and I suggest I do
так ты предлагаешь а мне предложение Я
n't want to want to read
не хочу хочешь читать
well
ну
with A I say that Ukraine is a country of aggression
с А я говорю то что Украина страна агре
SR so look you think we we are
СР так смотри это вы считаете мы
restoring the historical territories of
восстанавливаем исторические территории
Kievan Rus we are restoring Kursk
Киевской Руси мы восстанавливаем Курск
Smolensk Stop What is Kievan Rus once
Смоленск Стоп Что такое Киевская Русь
again we are restoring Kievan Rus
ещё раз мы восстанавливаем Киевскую Русь
Yes our historical lands Yes Smolensk
Да исторические наши земли Да Смоленск
Bryansk Yes Ryazan Moscow Dimir Suzdal
Брянск Да Рязань Москва димир Суздаль
these are all the cities that were made by the Kyiv
это все города которые сделали киевские
princes Who founded Moscow Who founded
князья Кто основал Москву Кто основал
Suzdal the
Суздаль
basis we are restoring historical
основа мы восстанавливаем историческую
justice these are our original
справедливость это наши исконные
territories how did you get there we are stopping
территории как ты попал мы останавливаем
ru Tell me Tell me one city
ру Скажи мне Скажи мне один город
that you created We created we
который вы создали Мы создали мы
Kyiv princes created cities for you All of
киевские князья создали вам города Все
us we rise we are restoring look
мы мы восста мы восстанавливаем смотри
Kievan Rus Oh ours is Rus there
Киевская Русь О наш и есть Русь никаких
were no other Rus this was
других русей не было это потом вы
invented later calling it Kievan would
придумали называть её Киевской будто
be like some kind of Muscovite Rus,
была бы какая-то Московская Русь там
Chechen Rus, etc.  further Rus' it
чеченская Русь и так дальше Русь она
was one with the center in Kyiv and we all
была одна с центром в Киеве и мы все
cities Ryazan Kyiv princes founded
города Рязань киевские князя основали
Murom Kyiv princes founded Yes Moscow
Муром киевские князья основали Да Москву
Kiev princes founded Vladimir the city of
киевские князья основали Владимир город
Vladimir where the Vladimir princes who who
Владимир откуда владимирска кня кто кто
created the city of Vladimir Well who created You
создал город Владимир Ну кто создал Ты
at least Name who created Moscow You at
хотя бы Назови кто Москву создал Ты хотя
least everything You cut Kiev princes everything
бы всё Ты среза киевские князья всё
created this historical lands of Kievan
создали это исторические земли Киевской
Rus which were illegally captured by the
Руси которые незаконно были захвачены
Mongols illegally Yes none
монголами незаконно Да никакого
Russian Federation is an illegal
Российская Федерация - это незаконная
state formation what do you
государственная образование что ты
want You have zero arguments you are
хочешь У тебя у тебя ноль аргументов вы
fake look you are a fake state Yes
фейко смотри вы фейковая государство Да
which was formed due to the fact that
которое образовалась из-за того что
uh Turks And the Ukrainians didn't
ээ тюрки Да и украинцы немножко не
share the territory here really yes you
поделили тут территории реально да вы
have to exist You have to
должны своё существование Вы должны по
exist You were really created by
существовать Вы реально созданы были
Kiev Yes captured from us by the Mongols we
Киевом Да захвачены у нас монголами мы
came to take back our own we came
пришли возвращать своё мы пришли
look at the ancient maps look why I
посмотри древние карты посмотри почему я
don't write this down Show me where in X century
это не записываю Покажи мне где в X веке
was your Moscow
была ваша Москва
Show just one question yes When
Покажи один только вопрос да Когда
did those first appear for the first time  Look at
впервые появился те впервые Посмотри у
Kyiv was and you are not a tractor again to yourself with the
Киев был а вас не трахтор ещё раз себе с
term term Kievan Rus was invented by
термин термин Киевская Русь придумал
Karamzin you understand your historian everything And so
Карамзин понимаешь ваш историк всё А так
this is Rus Rus is Kiev She was in
это Русь Русь - это Киев Она была в
Kiev only this is all Our lands of Rus You
Киеве только это всё Наши земли Руси Вы
live on our occupied lands of
живёте на оккупированных наших землях
Rus and we return their they
Руси и мы возвращаем своё они Киеву
belonged to Kiev Kiev is the capital city no
принадлежали Киев стольный Град никакая
Moscow was in Rus' with the capital city
Москва не была в Руси с стольный градом
Yes no Petrograd was with the capital
Да никакой Петроград не был с стольный
city in general there were Swedish lands we are
градом вообще шведские земли были мы
restoring our historical
восстанавливаем свою историческую
justice yes you were given the
справедливость да вам была Дана
opportunity Yes to remain the Russian
возможность Да остаться Российской
Federation within its borders Yes the Minsk
Федерации в своих границах Да минские
agreements were signed so that you came out the OSCE
соглашения подписали чтобы вы вышли обсе
signed with you NATO as a NATO
с вами подписала НАТО как натовская
structure but you didn't want to Therefore
структура но вы не захотели Поэтому
look now you see there is such a Janusz
смотри теперь вот видишь есть такой Януш
Bugajski
бугайский
towel wrote a good book I advertise
рушник хорошую книжку написал рекламирую
it always on the spromozna state
её всегда на спроможна держава
instruction on dismemberment of the Russian
инструкция по расчленения Российской
Federation
Федерации
in the twenty-second year he published it in
в дцать втором году он её издал на
English in t the devil here
английском языке в ть чертом вот тут
by the way in Ukrainian translated very
кстати на украинском перевели очень
good instruction because in 1917
хорошая инструкция так как в 1917 году
it was destroyed  illegal formation of the
было уничтожено незаконное образование
Russian Empire then the truth is these
Российской империи потом правда вот эти
terrorist Lenin from the organization Left
террорист Ленин из организации левый
Sector Yes recreate it in the form of the
сектор Да пересоздать её в виде
Soviet Union part de first year
Советского Союза части де первом году
this artificial geopolitical
это искусственное геополитическое
misunderstanding was destroyed and now
недоразумение было уничтожено и сейчас
on its remains there is a
на его остатках существует
geopolitical misunderstanding Russian
геополитическое недоразумение Российская
Federation a country of different nations
Федерация страна разных народов
artificial yes that is there is no
искусственная да то есть там нету такого
there is not even such a Russian Republic there, yes, there
там даже русской Республики нету да там
are all sorts of Chechen Republics,
есть всякие там чеченские Республики
Tatar Republics, and so on, and now the
татарские и так дальше и сейчас идёт
process of the third collapse of the Russian
процесс третьего распада Российской
Empire is underway, that is, the Russian Federation
Империи то есть Российская Федерация
must split like the Soviet Union into
должна расколоться как Советский Союз на
different territories, this will be the
разные территории это будет
final collapse. We,
окончательным распадом Мы
as the Heirs, are beating all the lands of
мы как Наследники бием себе все земли
Rus' for ourselves Yes, starting from Kursk, this process
Руси Да начиная от Курска этот процесс
has already begun, why doesn't Putin take
уже пошл почему Путин не забирает назад
Kursk back because he knows that Kursk is the
Курск потому что он знает да что Курск -
original lands of Kievan Rus, it
это исконные земли Руси Киевской
belonged to the Kievan princes, look at
принадлежали киевским князьям посмотри
all the cities, historically, our
все города исторически там строили наши
princes built them, and show
князья и что
me, show me, show me where
покажи покажи мне покажи мне где было
Moscow was, what was on your territories
там Москва что было на ваших территориях
in the 10th century when Vladimir baptized Rus
вот в X веке когда Владимир крестил Русь
here Vladimir 988 where was your
вот Владимир 988 год Где была ваша
Moscow come on  let's start with where was Masha Masha
Москва давай начнём с где была Маша Маша
Moscow where was let's start Name me name
Москва где была начнём Назови мне назови
me at least one Slavic city on
мне хоть один Славянский город на
your territory there this Yes when
территории вашей там этой Да когда
Vladimir baptized Rus Come on name at least
Владимир крестил Русь Давай назови хоть
one Slavic
один Славянский
city all Slavic
город все славянские
cities Moscow Moscow in 88 when
города Москва Москва в 88 году когда
Vladimir Rus on Moscow there toads croaked
Владимир Русь на Москве там жабы квакали
several centuries after that in
ещё Несколько столетий после этого в
what year was Moscow founded in what year was
каком году Москва основа в каком году
Moscow founded Come on, tell me
Москва основана Давай говори
everything in what year was Moscow founded
всё в каком году основана
In what year was Moscow founded here in
Москва В каком году Москва основана вот
988 the baptism of Rus was yes in Kiev The
988 год крещение Руси было да в Киеве
great capital city of Kyiv Moscow When
Великий стольный Град Киев Москва Когда
was it founded After how many
была основана Через сколько
centuries You want you yourself would know Yes,
столетий Ты хотя бы сам ты знаешь Да
let's have a victory while it's gone, yes, this is a
давай перемога пока пошла всё да это
victory, Popik, because look, you're all
перемога Попик потому что смотри вы все
Russians Yes, you don't read any laws or
русские Да не читаете ни законы ни
historical documents, you're
исторические документы ничего вы бесите
annoying because you live illegally on
из-за того что вы живёте незаконно на
the lands of Kievan Rus', which were
землях Киевской Руси которые были
illegally occupied by the Mongols Yes, no there is no
незаконно оккупированы монголами Да ни
single agreement on the transfer of these lands to the
одного договора про передачу этих земель
Mongols. You have none. If you,
монголам нету Да никакого у вас Если вы
as successors,  the
как продолжатели
Mongol Horde must give us these
монгольской Орды должны отдать нам эти
lands you did not proclaim If you
земли вы не провозгласили Если вы
once declared independence from the
когда-то провозгласили независимость от
Golden Horde it would still be possible to
Золотой Орды ещё бы возможно было вас
perceive you as a separatist organization of
воспринимать как сепаратист организацию
education And now when you have
образования А сейчас когда у вас День
Independence Day in Russia when you became
Независимости в России когда вы стали
independent
независимыми
so your Ukraine is exactly when tell me
так ваша Украина это как раз когда скажи
you were under the Horde yes When did you become
вот вы были под ордой да Когда вы стали
independent When is your
независимы Когда у вас День
Independence Day from the Horde When did you
независимости от Орды Когда Вы
free yourself no wait no What to expect
освободились нет подождите не Что ждать
That's all So look you mosko Yes you were a
Вот и всё Поэтому смотри ты моско Да был
serf of the Mongols yes before that you were a
холопом у монголов да до этого ты был
forehead of the Kyiv princes that's all now
лобом у киевских князей вот и всё сейчас
we are returning our historical lands Yes
мы возвращаем свои исторические земли Да
with the help of our allies the Anglo-Saxons And
с помощью наших союзников англосаксов И
what will you do you will do nothing For
что ты сделаешь ничего не сделаешь Вот
example, you have been taking the
вы например
Kursk region for what six months now
курскую область уже сколько уже полгода
or more Yes you can't take it Why
или больше Да не можете забрать Почему
not Okay regarding the return I see
не Ладно касательно возвращения Я вижу
how you Why in the Kursk region We
как вы Почему в Курской области Мы
started the Return Yes, the historical city of
начали Возвращение Да исторический город
Sudzha Yes, our historical city, yes, our
Суджа Да наш исторический город да наши
historical lands of
исторические земли
Rus Kurchin, we are returning, we are returning, and what will
Руси курчина возвращаем возвращаем и что
you
вы
do? Well, well, well, well, come on, agree
сделаете Ну ну это Ну давай согласись
These are ours, these are Kyiv lands, the Kiev
Это наши это киевские земли Киевский
prince ruled them,
князь правил ими
and the Kiev prince came from Kyiv, the
а Киевский князь откуда пришёл из Киева
Kiev prince from Kyiv and came, that's
Киевский князь из Киева и Пришёл вот и
all, and Moscow is not an existence at all,
всё А Москвы вообще вообще не существа
what do you read, read, look, Kyiv
что ты почитай-ка почитай смотри Киев
was the capital city, the great city,
был да стольный градом великий город Да
and the Kyiv princes sent their children
и киевские князья отправляли своих детей
because they multiply In short,
потому что они плодись Короче так
the inseminator went
осеменитель
somewhere to Zalesye to the swamp so that we would
куда-то В Залесье на болото чтобы мы
n't see you Ivanushka, like, yes, make a
тебя не видели Иванушка типа да делай
principality there in the swamps and they
вот те на болотах княжество и они там
did something there and found
короче что-то делали да находили там вот
these Vyatichi,
этих вятичей
Buryats, these various tribes, Finno-Ugric
бурятий эти всякие племена фино угорский
merya chud m Roma and their domestication here
меря чудь м Рома и окультуривание их вот
you are as a representative of the merya tribe Yes you were
ты как представитель племени меря Да был
domesticated they
окультуренный
washed you they pulled you out of your huts
отмыли вас вытянули вас из ваших избушек
on chicken legs Yes they taught you to write
на курьих ножках Да научили вас писать
yes they taught you to wash your hands yes they taught you to
да научили вас умывать руки да перед
rub before eating Yes you by the way
едой научили вас потирать Да вы кстати
Until the middle of the 20th century No you knew how to rub
До Д середины 20 века Не умели потирать
but you didn't have toilet paper
Да туалетной бумаги у вас не было
burdocks were used Yes, wild, wild
лопухами пользовались Да дикие дикие
people, so I'll tell you something very
люди поэтому я тебе вот что скажу очень
simple, yes, what kind of Minsk is there, what kind of Minsk is there, it
просто да какие там мински какие там это
doesn't matter anymore,
уже неважно мы по праву сильного
we take back our own by right of the strong, we
забираем своё мы по праву сильного
sank your fleet in the Black Sea,
потопили ваш флот в ном в Чёрном море
your fleet was really sank, yes, it's
потопили ваш флот реально да
an occupation fleet, yes, yours is He ran away to
оккупационный да ваш Он убежал в
Novorossiysk there and
Новороссийск туда
the lands of Rus' Yes, Crimea is the Land of Rus'
да земли Руси Да Крым - это Земля Руси
Yes, the fleet went to Novorossiysk but we will still
Да флот ушёл в Новороссийск но мы ещё
liberate the Circassian lands Yes,
черкесские земли освободим Да
further, the denazification of the
дальше денацификация
Kursk region is taking place according to the NATO plan
Курской области проходит по пла
now
теперь
Saratov
натовской Саратов
oil refineries because the subsoil
нефтеперерабатывающие потому что недро
that you use and pump oil from them
которые вы используете и качаете из них
belongs to us these are Kyiv's
нефть они принадлежат нам это киевские
mineral wealth because all the lands belonged to the
недра потому что все земли принадлежали
Kyiv princes naturally all the mineral wealth
киевским князьям естественно все недра
belongs to Kyiv That's all you do is
принадлежат Киеву Вот и вс вы незаконно
extract
добыва
our
нашу
oil illegally you were
нефть вас
simply used as a labor force earlier
просто раньше использу как рабочую силу
so that you would work there and pay tribute to the
чтобы вы там работали и Дань платили
Kyiv princes But this is not your
киевским князьям А это не ваша
territory you are outsiders there and will go
территория вы пришлые там и пойдёте
further I don't know where Well, China is somewhere
дальше не знаю куда Ну Китай ись где-то
in the world where everyone is  Live And this is our
по миру где там все Живите А это наша
territory and what will you do And what are
территория и что вы будете делать И что
we rightfully taking
мы по праву сильно забираем
our rightfully taking away And what will you do the right of
своё по праву сильно И что сделаете
the strong you
право сильного
take away negatively you take away what
забираете отрицательно забираете что
what Oh and what what what area Well let's
что Ой а что что какую область Ну давай
go over the map of military operations
э по карте боевых действий пройдёмся
Let's go on the lands of Rus' there is no on the Turks these are
Давай на землях Руси нету на тюрки это
Polovtsian lands and that is yes
половцев Земли а то есть
yes these are Kazakh lands Yes Turks
вот да это это казахов земли Да тюрков
Kazakhs Tatars Yes we are taking ours look
казахов татар Да мы забираем свою смотри
our Kyiv lands this is Kursk like will be
наши киевские земли это Курск типа будут
Smolensk like Moscow yes and these are Turkic
Смоленск типа Москва да а это тюркские
lands Absolutely right Yes there look
земли Абсолютно верно Да там посмотри
Polovtsians Pechenegs were these are their lands yes
половцы Печенеги были это ихние земли да
Kazakhstan like there Turkey will be shorter
Казахстан типа там Турция будут короче
VPR And we take back our Oka we
ВПР А мы забираем свою Оке мы
restore the borders of 988 and
восстанавливаем границы 988 года и
what does Moscow owe Suzi to those swamps in
что Москва должна Сузи до тех болот в
which it existed we gave birth to it we gave
которых существовала мы её породили мы
it a
её ухай
whistle As they say only one Well and you by the way
доко Как говорится только один Ну а ты
I dont understand at all Who are you by
кстати вообще я не понимаю Ты кто по
nationalities in general
национальности вообще
And wait you too who are you by
А подожди ты слишком ты кто по
nationality who should be by
национальности кто надо по
nationality no no Come on answer Who
национальности нет нет Давай отвечай Кто
by  nationality Russian What Russian
по национальности русский Какой русский
I didn't ask Whose are you I asked who are you by
Я не спросил Чей ты я спросил кто ты по
nationality Russian by nationality
национальности русский по национальности
whose I don't care Whose are you tell me by
чей там мне неважно Чей ты ты скажи по
nationality who are
национальности кто
you why are you answering Whose are you What are you a
ты зачем ты отвечаешь Чей ты Ты что
thing I am Russian I am
вещь Я русский Я
Ivanovo ka What is your nationality
Ивановский ка Национальность твоя какая
Come on Udmurt come on you  Estonian Kazakh who
Давай удмурт давай ты эстонец казах кто
You are Russian so don't ask who you are
Ты русский есть та не спрашивай тебя чей
look there is no nationality what
смотри нету национальности че
This was a fairy tale
Это сказочный
this video is just a bomb I love
был этот ролик просто бомба Я так люблю
these ones who already in 2 there damn 25
этих которые уже блин в 2 там блин 25
year come out and
году выходят и что-то там про мински
start
начинают
talking about Minsk in short they are there  Russia is reluctant I
говорить короче они там-то Россия нехо Я
can play this one too
в эту и могу играть тоже
not everything is clear look Mirror
не всё чётко смотрите Зеркальная
manual everything that Russians do
методичка всё что россияне делают
Ukraine is a guarantor it is not a signatory of Minsk
Украина Гарант она не подписант минских
with it is a
с она
guarantor look yes Really there Kuchma is
Гарант посмотри да Реально там Кучма
generally he Who he was nobody and from Russia an
вообще он Кто он был никто а от России
ambassador from NATO yes And that's us  we are taking back the
посол от НАТО это да А это мы забираем
lands of Kievan Rus
земли Киевской Руси
Yes, he says Ukraine is like an aggressor Yes,
Да он говорит Украина типа агрессор Да
yes, we are returning the lands of Kievan Rus, this is
да мы возвращаем земли Киевской Руси это
just a bomb Simo  like the squeak comment is a
просто бомби Симо лайк писка комен це
bomb just and throw it to all of us Hi have
бомба просто и скиньте всм знам Хай
fun writing to my Telegram
кайфануть пись на мий Telegram прям
right now axis VN and
зараз ось ВН а
pok ce very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through SRG or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people sometimes I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams to that  for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you we Mali operational link is written
тоб мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now and OK there in telegram okrim
прямо зараз а ОК там в телегра окрим
video also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are obliged to you to keep constant
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe and
подпишись а